Curto, Ernest; Papers apap238
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislative Correspondence, 1944; 1946-1965; Undated; 3; 4.0 cubic ft.
  As it was unclear how the general correspondence subseries was originally organized, the archivist arranged it chronologically. Researchers should note, as mentioned above, that this series contains bills from the earlier years of Curto’s service in the legislature. Bills from the later years are individually filed in the bills series.
  - Constituent Correspondence, 1944; 1951-1964; Undated; 3.1
    - Lewiston, Annexation, 1952; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 1-2)
    - Lewiston, Annexation- Map, 1952 (Oversized 1, Folder 9)
    - Lewiston, Town of, 1958-1959; 1961-1962 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 3)
    - Lewiston, Town of, 1953; 1961; 1963; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 4)
    - Lewiston, Town of (Completed), 1961-1962 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 5)
    - Lewiston, Town of (Completed), 1962; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 6)
    - Lewiston, Town of (Completed), 1962-1963; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 7)
    - Lewiston, Town of (Completed), 1964; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 8)
    - Lockport, Town of (Completed), 1963; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 9)
    - Lockport, City of (Completed), 1962; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 10)
    - Lockport, City of (Completed), 1963-1964; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 11)
    - Niagara County, 1958-1963 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 12)
    - Niagara County, 1960 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 13)
    - Niagara County, 1960-1964; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 14)
    - Niagara County, 1962-1963 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 15)
    - Niagara County Board of Supervisors (Helen C. Boyer), 1959-1961 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 16)
    - Niagara County Board of Supervisors (Helen C. Boyer), 1962-1963 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 17)
    - Niagara County (Completed), 1962 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 18)
    - Niagara County Legislation, 1964-1965 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 20)
    - Niagara County, Loss of Assessment (Completed), 1961 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 22)
    - Niagara County (Completed), 1963 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 19)
    - Niagara County, Legislation Pending, 1963 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 21)
    - Niagara County, Miscellaneous Matter Completed, 1960; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 23)
    - Niagara County, Miscellaneous Matters Pending, 1960; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 24)
    - Niagara County School Districts, 1961-1962; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 25)
    - Niagara, Town of, Annexation, 1952; 1959 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 26)
    - Niagara, Town of, Annexation, 1944; 1951-1953; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 27)
    - Niagara, Town of, Annexation, 1952; 1954-1955; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 28)
    - Niagara, Town of, Annexation, 1952; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 29)
    - Niagara Falls Airport Annexation, 1960 (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 30)
    - Niagara Falls Airport Annexation- Maps, 1960 (Oversized 1, Folder 10)
    - Niagara Falls, City of- Maps, 1954; 1957 (Oversized 1, Folder 11)
    - Niagara Falls, City of, 1955-1956; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 31)
    - Niagara Falls, City of, 1962; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 32)
    - Niagara Falls, City of (Closed), 1959-1963; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 33-34)
    - Niagara Falls, City of (Completed), 1964; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 35-36)
    - Niagara Falls, City of (Completed), 1962-1963; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 37-39)
    - Niagara Falls, City of (Completed) (folder 1 of 3), 1964; Undated (Box 15 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 40)
    - Niagara Falls, City of (Completed) (folders 2-3 of 3), 1964; Undated (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 1-2)
    - Niagara Falls, City of, Legislation Pending, 1960 (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 3)
    - Niagara Falls, City of, Miscellaneous Data, 1964 (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 4)
    - Niagara Falls, City of (Pending), 1964 (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 5)
    - Niagara Falls, City of, Power Authority, 1955-1956; 1958; Undated (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 6)
    - Niagara Falls, City of, Wards Increase, 1955; Undated (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, 1946-1965; Undated; 3.2
    - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 10-11)
    - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 12-13)
    - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 14-17)
    - Correspondence, 1951 (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 18-20)
    - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 21-22)
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 23-25)
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 16 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 26-29)
    - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 17 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 17 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 2-3)
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 17 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 4-11)
    - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 17 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 12-18)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 17 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 19-22)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 17 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 18 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 1-6)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 18 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 7-10)
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 18 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 11-19)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 18 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Undated (Box 18 (3-Legislative Correspondence), Folder 21)